

0723 014 344

contact@sebastianc.dev

mww.sebastianc.dev



#### SUMMARY

As a front-end developer with skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and more, I aim to provide an easier experience for the users and to focus on their problems firstly, rather than on the technical ones. Willing to continuously gather new skills and expand my actual ones, I do everything to stay up-to-date with the latest technologies of the mad, but beautiful, front-end development world.

/in/sebastianciobanu

@s3bastian43

/s3bastian43



## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Tremend (Vodafone) | Aug 2019 - Present Bucharest, Romania

At Vodafone, I am responsible for implementing as well as improving various features for both mobile & web applications.

### JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

SIVECO | Sept 2018 - Aug 2019

Bucharest, Romania

My role within the company is to analyse, test and develop back-end and front-end code for the multiple projects I am working on.

### JUNIOR WEB DESIGNER

Easitill | Oct 2017 - June 2018

Brixworth, United Kingdom

My responsibilities included the designing, the prototyping and the development of e-commerce and brochure websites, as well as improving brand

identity, SEO and performance.

# **PROJECTS**

#### LIVING INNOVATION | 2019

"LIVIN" is a complex online platform for discussion, knowledge creation and collaboration on new solutions that are beneficial to society and create new business opportunities. My role on this project was to improve the overall user experience through engaging UI design as well as working on the actual front-end implementation.

living-innovation.net

### UNIPLANNER | 2018

Student planner and team collaboration web application created so that the users can keep track of their course, as well as collaborate by sharing notes and creating tasks.

uniplanner.co.uk

#### HOME-START NORTHAMPTON | 2017-2018

Working in a team of four, the WordPress CMS was used to develop a website that reflects and promotes the support offered by the charity.

homestart-northampton.org.uk



**EDUCATION** 

# BSc BUSINESS COMPUTING (WEB DESIGN)

WordPress

University of Northampton | 2015 - 2018

Northampton, United Kingdom

### AWARDS

- Most promising first year student on BSc Business Computing at The University of Northampton | 2016
- High Achievers A Level Scholarship | 2015

#### SKILLS

Development

HTMI 5 CSS3 | SASS JavaScript | ES6

Reactis React Native Node.js | Express.js PHP

Drupal Jekyll SEO | WPO Bootstrap Material UI SOL | MySOL Git | SVN MongoDB

Desian

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign Iconography UX | UI Design

UI Design Material Design Flat Design Microinteractions Storymapping **Emotional Interaction** Social Interaction

IDE | Prototyping

Visual Studio Code WebStorm PhpStorm Balsamig Adobe XD

InVision App

Figma